Hey, can you speak?
Guess not.
Please wake up!
You're a good guy!
Don't become a bad guy!
What is this creature?!
Thank you for stopping me.
Hold on...
Are you back to normal?
Seems like it.
Yay! Yay!
He's back!
Are you saying that creature
was controlling you?
I really want to tell you
everything,
but first, could you please untie me?
It's so uncomfortable,
I can't stand it.
What do you think, Keiji?
If he starts rampaging,
I'll take care of him.
I'm finally free!
Oh?
My arms fell off...
That's so gross!
Well, I didn't expect to
be saved by chickens...
Thank you so much.
Oh, you're the one
from the other day...
You remember me?
Yeah.
My body may have been possessed,
but my mind and heart were intact.
Even though I was being controlled,
I am deeply sorry.
So the Devils were
behind all of this.
Yeah, it was back then...
When that creature lodged itself
in my brain,
I immediately sprouted arms.
And I lost all control of my body.
I shudder, thinking
I was parasitized by
this disgusting creature!
You're kinda disgusting yourself,
Old Man Octopus!
My, you've got no shame,
Little Chick!
To think the Devils had
such an ability.
They're on another level
from the Demons.
So that's how they collected all
the Demons in the abandoned factory...
By the way, have you seen
this Demon before?
Ah, it's one of the ones
they brought in recently.
He was in the warehouse.
What are the Devils planning?
Do they want to destroy all the cities
and make humans suffer?
Nope. That was just to
let off some steam.
Let off some steam?
If we don't let off some steam
here and there,
we end up rampaging.
I suspect we were under a lot of
stress.
So, what are their true motives?
That... I don't know.
But I did overhear them once...
Damn it, no leads again.
Don't sweat it, Yuji.
Let's take our time searching.
Search?
Search for what?
That's not important.
Take me to the abandoned factory.
I'm going to save Morio.
B-But how?
Old Man Octopus came
to his senses...
...so there's got to be a way.
I want to help too!
Do you understand the situation,
Piyoko?!
There's a horde of Demons
laying in wait!
I know that even if I go,
I won't be much help.
But I want to help save Morio!
I want to help your friend, Mister!
Piyoko...
I-I understand
how everyone feels, but...
The Devils are dangerously strong.
We should come up with a strategy
and proceed with caution.
I knew it...
You're scared of them.
B-Brother, you haven't seen them
in real life.
I've fought them firsthand!
You couldn't even beat me...
How can you even think—
- you can win?
- It doesn't matter who wins.
I'm gonna save Morio.
That's all there is to it.
I hate to admit it, but...
Big Brother is totally right.
I don't stand a chance,
being scared like this.
I can do this!
I'll save Father!
No matter what!
Keiji.
Sorry, I just realized there's someone
I have to meet up with.
I'll meet up with you
as soon as I'm done.
Got it.
Hold on, Morio!
PAPA!
ELIZABETH!
I'VE MISSED YOU, ELIZABETH!
P-PAPA I CAN'T BREATHE!
I'M SORRY.
IT'S BEEN SIX MONTHS!
He's amazing.
His mastery of Chickenese
continues to progress!
Papa, did you bring
what I requested?
Yes, it's all ready.
Bring it.
Here you are, Miss Elizabeth.
Amazing! All this,
completed in only 4 hours?!
I had my Yonezaka Group get
to work on it right away.
We're very proud of the results.
We did everything that we could
to add in all of the functions
that you requested.
Thank you, Papa!
It was nothing, Elizabeth.
But... why do you need
something like this?
I met a Demon
who changed my worldview.
I realized that only killing Demons
isn't the only way to solve problems.
I see.
You truly are a kind child.
I love you, Elizabeth.
I love you too, Papa.
EPISODE 9:
GONE TO THE BIRDS
We've been expecting you.
Is that little chick part
of your gang too?
Seems tough.
Let my father go!
Father?
Oh, you're his son?
You two look nothing alike—!
Huh. Your friend isn't half bad.
Nice. We've got ourselves
a live one.
Hey scumbag,
what did you do with Morio?
Morio?
Oh, must be the Demon Mama captured.
So, this is the one...
Those others that you speak of...
One of them might be
a rooster that I know well.
I knew he would eventually show up.
But I didn't expect them to join up
as a family and come here.
It's a bit earlier that
I would have liked, but...
It might be time to hunt
that one down.
Listen to me, Hikari.
You must not kill that one.
But do as you please with the rest.
But be very careful, understand?
Yes, Mama.
Isn't your goal to
eradicate Demons?
Why are you risking your life
for one pathetic Demon?
Pathetic... Demon?
Morio put his life on the line
to save people.
You don't know the first thing
about him.
You forced him to assault
the same humans he fought to protect.
The pain and guilt he felt...
doing the opposite of what he believed in.
It must have been hard for him.
His heart must've been screaming in pain.
- Morio's kind, so it must've been torture.
- Keiji!
It's unforgiveable.
You stomped on Morio's heart,
so now,
you're going to pay for it.
You make my crown curl!
Friendship... and familial bonds, huh?
All that's meaningless in the end...
Fine.
We can let them go.
In exchange...
...we're gonna have you play
with some of our friends.
Hold on tight, Piyoko.
G-Got it!
The game starts now!
Don't kill the one with
the red crown.
But you can slaughter the rest.
Damn it, I can't find an opening
to use my Kokekokko.
That's it!
Kokekokko!
Take this!
Totem Ko!
I've got no time to waste.
If I can't defeat the Devils...
...I'll wipe out the rest!
Rapid Wind Strike!
Hatsu!
Triple!
Ten!
Fifth Heavenly Path!
Explosive Dragon Strike!
Not bad, not bad!
Look at them go!
Hey, Hikari...
Can I go out there soon?
Nope.
Damn it. This is annoying...
That's it, I'm killing you all at once!
Don't kill them!
Sorry I'm late.
Elizabeth!
They're not dead...
Did you just do that with
that machine?
Yes.
The DEG, or Digital Energy Gun, Raijin.
Concussions will leave them
paralyzed for the next 2-3 days.
I'm glad this worked immediately.
Among this horde of possessed Demons,
might be another kind Demon like Morio,
or the Octopus Demon.
I want good Demons to survive!
Y-You're so amazing, Miss Elizabeth!
Not bad!
Oh, another one showed up.
Well, why don't we raise
the stakes a little, then?
Morio!
Morio! It's me!
Keiji!
Hey, you son of a–!
Snap out of it, man!
So, what are you gonna do now?
I'm going to wake Morio up!
I leave those two big ones to you!
Got it!
Kokekokko!
Mister, don't!
Morio will die if you do that!
The parasite should be
inside his head!
If I kill the parasite,
maybe I can set him free!
Kokekokko!
Damn it, it's no use.
Mister...
I will save Morio.
What did you say?
I think I'm small enough to
climb inside of Morio's head.
If I can defeat the monster
inside his body,
Morio will return to his old self.
Are you insane?
You know that's impossible—
We won't know unless we try!
I've been by your side
watching how you fight every fight.
So I can fight!
No, but you...
Yes, I can! It's the only way!
You might die, you know.
I won't die,
until I'm by your side, Mister!
I knew it,
it's not powerful enough.
Oh yeah, then...
...how about this?!
Raijin Shot Full Charge!
All right!
I can use this as my weapon.
You'll need some rope with you too.
I'm ready to go!
Hop on, Piyoko!
R-Roger!
How do we get you inside?!
Um... um...
Maybe through his nose!
Damn it. This is annoying.
Hey, Morio!
Let me get inside your head!
Stand still
so I can save you, dummy!
Piyoko, I think the only way is
to have Elizabeth use her gun
to knock him out.
I see! That could work!
In that case, leave it to me!
I overheard your plan.
You're very brave, little one.
- Old Man Octopus!
- Octopops!
Now, little chick!
Don't worry
I'm stronger than I look.
I'll keep him restrained.
Thank you, Octopops!
Fifth Fist Heavenly Path!
Explosive Chicken Leg!
Hikari... Isn't time?
Are you okay, Piyoko?
I-I just got surprised.
It's not too late to turn back.
I'm going in!
I've already decided!
Good luck, lil' chick!
I'm gonna help the Mister!
I can do this if I give it my all!
Just you wait, Morio.
I'll save you, no matter what!
We're counting on you, Piyoko!
The brain must be up here.
Ugh! It's sticky and gross!
Huh?!
It's coming from that thing
that looks like a butthole.
I think I can use that to get there!
It's sticky...
It's so cramped in here.
It's so dark, I can't see anything!
It's still sticky too!
Ugh! It stinks too!
Need to spit!
Huh?!
What could that be?
I'm gonna follow the light.
It's getting narrow.
Oh, an exit!
Yay! I got out!
N-No way! I can't fight
that monster and win!
I'll hold this dam up,
even if it costs me my life!
Th-That's right!
I can't abandon someone so kind!
It's okay! I can win!
I gotta believe in myself!
I can...
DUTY
Do this!
I...
I won't lose!
It hurts! It really hurts!
I can't do this! I want to run away!
Huh?
This is...
This is Mister's feather...
This will be my good luck charm!
That's right...
No matter how hard and painful
it is...
He never gives up!
The Mister's on my side.
I can't run away now.
I am not gonna give up!
DUTY
Think!
There's gotta be a way to win.
Wait a minute.
DUTY
Why hasn't it moved from that spot?
This monster is...
connected to Morio's brain!
I get it!
It's not that it's not moving...
It can't!
I get it now.
Then this is the only way!
I'll attack from behind!
DUTY
Take that! And that, and that!
I can win! I can win!
Mi...
Mister...
You're all very brave.
You've finally managed to drag those
Devils out into the open!
Next Time:
To Back a Bird Into a Corner
Nevertheless, dear Little Chick...
Are you actually all alone?
FAN ART CONTEST AWARDS